[
  {
    "question": "I am a number between 30 and 50. I am a multiple of 6. When divided by 7, I have a remainder of 4. What number am I?",
    "options": [
      "36",
      "42",
      "46",
      "48"
    ],
    "answer": "42"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bus A leaves the interchange every 10 minutes. Bus B leaves every 15 minutes. They both left at 9:00 AM. What time will they leave together again?",
    "options": [
      "9:15 AM",
      "9:25 AM",
      "9:30 AM",
      "10:00 AM"
    ],
    "answer": "9:30 AM"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mrs. Lee wants to cut a piece of paper measuring 12 cm by 18 cm into squares. She wants the squares to be as BIG as possible with no paper left over. What is the length of each square?",
    "options": [
      "2 cm",
      "3 cm",
      "6 cm",
      "4 cm"
    ],
    "answer": "6 cm"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following numbers has an ODD number of factors?",
    "options": [
      "10",
      "12",
      "9",
      "15"
    ],
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "The sum of the first two Common Multiples of 3 and 4 is:",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "24",
      "36",
      "7"
    ],
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am a factor of 48 and a multiple of 4. The sum of my digits is 3. What number am I?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "24",
      "48",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "A bag of sweets can be shared equally among 3 friends, 4 friends, or 6 friends with NO leftovers. What is the smallest possible number of sweets in the bag?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "24",
      "18",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "If you add 2 to me, I become a multiple of 5. If you subtract 2 from me, I become a multiple of 4. What number am I?",
    "options": [
      "18",
      "23",
      "28",
      "33"
    ],
    "answer": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the difference between the 4th multiple of 8 and the 3rd multiple of 9.",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "1",
      "32",
      "27"
    ],
    "answer": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the smallest 2-digit number that has 2, 3, and 4 as its factors?",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "24",
      "36",
      "10"
    ],
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Farmer John has fewer than 50 eggs. If he counts them in groups of 7, he has 1 left over. If he counts them in groups of 9, he has 1 left over. How many eggs does he have?",
    "options": [
      "64",
      "46",
      "37",
      "28"
    ],
    "answer": "64"
  },
  {
    "question": "I am the largest 2-digit common factor of 30 and 45.",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "10",
      "15",
      "30"
    ],
    "answer": "15"
  }
]